O.k.
now one thing to keep in mind here is, if you wanted to go just with gold fish you wouldn't need the heater, o.k.
Those are, gold fish are cold water fish, their very, basically, glorified carp and you could, you wouldn't want a heater.
However, if you go with tropical fish you're going to want to be a little more careful because they?re not as durable as gold fish.
Now, as far as number of fish, to go with, a good rule of thumb is one, one inch of fish per gallon.
So, in other words, in a, in a, in a tank that's a ten gallon tank like this, about ten inches of fish.
You can break that down, you know, ten one inch fish or, or five two inch fish.
Now obviously if you get a ten inch fish, yeah he could live in here but, you get to a ten inch fish Oscar, something like that, you're going to want to go with a bigger tank, cause that's not going to be really fair to the fish to go with a ten inch fish in this, this, this small of a tank, wouldn't be fair to, to, the fish and you wouldn't enjoy it either.
So, so that's what we're looking at here as far as fish.
Obviously if you get a much bigger filter, you could probably fit more, more fish in there but for, for what we're doing here, basic, small, appropriate filter, bout, bout ten inches of fish in this tank.
And, as you can see they're kind of spread out here so they're using the plants.
And, and of course you?re, your tropical fish pet person will help you with that too.
As far as selection of fish, that's where you might want to again rely on the, your pet shop expert.
Obviously, you're going to want some, some color, but just because a fish is colorful doesn't mean you can mix them, obviously you can't mix Piranha with Tetras.
If you're going to go with Piranha with is a carnivorous fish, you're going to want to stay with only Piranhas.
There's a lot of basic community fish, Molly's, Sword tails, Guppies, Neons, these are small colorful fish that get along well with each other and do fine in a tank together.
For the more serious hobbyist, you might want to go with Cichlids, if you go with Cichlids, you've got to stay with only Cichlids.
You can't mix Cichlids with gold fish or Cichlids with these, these community type of tropical fish.
If you go with South African Cichlids, you want to stay with South African, you don't want to mix them with South American Cichlids.
The, the, the African Cichlids are a more aggressive fish.
These are the kind of things that you should talk to your pet shop, tropical fish expert about, he'll know these things.
And, you can go from.